Finding Aid for Interfaith Council for Peace and Justice (Ann Arbor, Mich.) records, 1966-2010
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Interfaith Council for Peace and Justice (Ann Arbor, Mich.) records 1966-2010
Interfaith Council for Peace and Justice (Ann Arbor, Mich.)
85234 Ba 2; Ba Outsize
Records of the Interfaith Council For Peace and Justice, a Washtenaw County-based interdenominational organization encouraging participation in social justice education and activism. The collection is divided into twelve series, Chronological Files, Topical Files, Hunger Task Force, Clergy and Laity Concerned, Photographs and Audiovisual Materials, Steering Committee, Religious Coalition on Central America, Middle East Task Force, Racial and Economic Task Force, Disarmament Working Group, and Posters.
30 linear feet
1 oversize folders
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The records were received from the organization (donor no. 6539 ) in various accessions beginning in 1980.
Periodic additions to the records are expected.
The record group is open to research.
In December 1965, members of various Ann Arbor religious congregations established an organization with the purpose of coordinating their opposition to the Vietnam War. Eventually named the Interfaith Council For Peace, the group's key organizer was Barbara Fuller, a representative of Memorial Christian Church in Ann Arbor. The Interfaith Council was chartered as a local chapter of the larger, national anti-war coalition, Clergy and Laity Concerned about Vietnam (name later changed to Clergy and Laity Concerned).
As opposition to the Vietnam War grew, both CALC and the IFC arranged a continuing series of activities and events designed to increase public dissatisfaction with the war and bring the conflict to a speedy conclusion. Barbara Fuller, in addition to her responsibilities in Ann Arbor, became an important figure in CALC. She served as the organization's regional coordinator for the Midwest and also was a member of CALC's national executive board.
The eventual conclusion of the war led to a re-evaluation of purpose among all anti-war groups. In Ann Arbor the Interfaith Council for Peace turned its attention to questions of social justice, particularly amnesty, human rights and world hunger. The IFC became the coordinating agency for an annual "hunger walk" in the community, an event designed to both dramatize the plight of the starving and to educate local residents about this problem. In 1988, the organization formally changed its name to the Interfaith Council for Peace and Justice (ICPJ).
Through the 1990s and 2000s, the ICPJ was highly involved in a wide variety of activities at the local, state, national and international levels. The group's yearly and monthly listings of events attest to their ongoing dedication to peace and justice and their high level of activism during this time. They continued their administrative role of the annual CROP Walk and also raised awareness regarding local hunger, homelessness, and welfare issues. They also held numerous protests and vigils to raise public awareness about the war in Bosnia, the "School of Assassins" at Fort Benning, support for a nuclear test ban, and opposition to U.S. bombings in Iraq. In addition, they hosted annually a day of "peaceful" events in remembrance of the bombing of Hiroshima, and in the late 1990s began training and coordinating a "Peace Team" to staff the local KKK rallies and anti-KKK protests in Ann Arbor.
The files of the Interfaith Council have been arranged into twelve series: Chronological Files, Topical Files, Hunger Task Force, Clergy and Laity Concerned, Photographs and Audiovisual Materials, Steering Committee, Religious Coalition on Central America, Middle East Task Force, Racial and Economic Task Force, Disarmament Working Group, and Posters.
Subjects:
Amnesty.; Ann Arbor (Mich.); Arab-Israeli conflict--1993--Peace.; Civil rights--United States.; Disarmament.; Hunger.; Jewish-Arab relations.; Latin America--History--1980-; Peace--Societies, etc.; Race discrimination.; United States--Foreign relations--Latin America.; Vietnam War, 1961-1975.; Interfaith Council for Peace and Justice (Ann Arbor, Mich.)
Subjects - Visual Materials:
Ann Arbor (Mich.); Clergy and Laity Concerned (U.S.); Demonstrations.; Protest movements.; St. Clare of Assisi Episcopal Church (Ann Arbor, Mich.); Vietnam War, 1961-1975.
Contributors:
Clergy and Laity Concerned (U.S.)
Genre Terms:
Photographs.; Sound recordings.; Videotapes.
- Chronological Files undated, 1966-2010
  The Chronological Files series (7.4 linear feet) is comprised primarily of meeting minutes, correspondence, announcements of upcoming events, and newspaper clippings which document the history of the organization, its activities, and socio-political concerns, from 1966-2010. Also included in this series is the organization's Constitution and By-Laws.
  - Undated
    - Constitution and By-Laws (Box 1)
    - Newspaper Clippings (Box 1)
    - Correspondence (Box 1)
    - Meetings (Box 1)
    - Memos (Box 1)
    - Notes (Box 1)
    - Publications (Box 1)
  - 1966
    - General (Box 1)
  - 1967
    - General (Box 1)
  - 1968
    - Activities (Box 1)
    - Correspondence (Box 1)
    - Meetings (Box 1)
    - Memos (Box 1)
    - Publications (Box 1)
  - 1969
    - Correspondence (Box 1)
    - Dow Chemical (Box 1)
    - March Against Death (Box 1)
    - Meetings (Box 1)
    - Memorial Day Remembrance (Box 1)
    - Memos (Box 1)
    - New Year's Eve (Box 1)
    - Peace Now Letters (Box 1)
    - Political Prisoners in Vietnam (Box 1)
    - Publications (Box 1)
  - 1970
    - Peter Blood Trial (Box 1)
    - CALC Convention (Box 1)
    - Correspondence (Box 1)
    - Draft Vigil (Box 1)
    - Exploration Group (Box 1)
    - Financial Appeals (Box 1)
    - General Mailings (Box 1)
    - Meetings (Box 1)
    - Membership (Box 1)
    - Memos (Box 1)
    - New Year's Eve (Box 1)
    - Peace Vigil (Box 1)
    - Publications (Box 1)
    - Town Meeting (Box 1)
  - 1971
    - Malcolm Boyd (Box 1)
    - Fred Branfman (Box 1)
    - Classified Research (Box 1)
    - Correspondence (Box 1)
    - Daily Death Toll Project (Box 1)
    - Davis Bill (Box 1)
    - Marvin Esch (Box 1)
    - Financial Appeals (Box 1)
    - Laos Rally (Box 1)
    - Letters To The Editor (Box 1)
    - Mailings (Box 1)
    - Memos (Box 1)
    - Meetings (Box 1)
    - Membership (Box 1)
    - Mother's Day Cards (Box 1)
    - Passover Peace Seder (Box 1)
    - Peace Fair (Box 1)
    - Peoples Peace Treaty (Box 1)
    - Political (Box 1)
    - POW Program (Box 1)
    - Publications (Box 2)
    - Toronto Visit (Box 2)
    - University of Michigan Classified Research and Vietnam (Box 2)
    - George Wald (Box 2)
    - Winter Soldier Investigation (Box 2)
  - 1972
    - Correspondence (Box 2)
    - Crater Memorial (Box 2)
    - Financial Appeals (Box 2)
    - Honeywell Campaign (Box 2)
    - Indochina Peace Campaign (Box 2)
    - Meetings (Box 2)
    - Memos (Box 2)
    - Migrant Action (Box 2)
    - Publications (Box 2)
    - University of Michigan Classified Research (Box 2)
  - 1973
    - Correspondence (Box 2)
    - Financial (Box 2)
    - Financial Appeals (Box 2)
    - Honeywell Campaign (Box 2)
    - Indochina Peace Campaign (Box 2)
    - Log, 2 folders (Box 2)
    - Meetings (Box 2)
    - Memos (Box 2)
    - Publications (Box 2)
  - 1974
    - Amnesty Action Group (Box 2)
    - Correspondence (Box 2)
    - Indochina Peace Campaign (Box 2)
    - Log, 2 folders (Box 2)
    - Memos (Box 2)
    - Meetings (Box 2)
  - 1975
    - Finance Committee (Box 2)
    - General (Box 2)
    - Indochina Peace Campaign (Box 2)
    - Log, 3 folders (Box 2)
  - 1976
    - Disarmament/Nuclear Freeze (Box 2)
    - General (Box 2)
    - Log (Box 2)
  - 1977
    - Activities (Box 2)
    - Correspondence (Box 2)
    - Disarmament/Nuclear Freeze (Box 2)
    - General (Box 2)
    - Log (Box 2)
  - 1978
    - Correspondence (Box 2)
    - Disarmament/Nuclear Freeze (Box 2)
    - General (Box 2)
  - 1979
    - Disarmament/Nuclear Freeze (Box 3)
    - General (Box 3)
  - 1980
    - Disarmament/Nuclear Freeze (Box 3)
    - General (Box 3)
  - 1981
    - Disarmament/Nuclear Freeze (Box 3)
    - General (Box 3)
  - 1982
    - Disarmament/Nuclear Freeze (Box 3)
    - General (Box 3)
    - Minutes and Agendas (Box 3)
  - 1983
    - Disarmament/Nuclear Freeze (Box 3)
    - General (Box 3)
    - Minutes and Agendas (Box 3)
  - 1984
    - Disarmament/Nuclear Freeze (Box 3)
    - General (Box 3)
    - Minutes and Agendas (Box 3)
  - 1985
    - Disarmament/Nuclear Freeze (Box 3)
    - General (Box 3)
    - Minutes and Agendas (Box 3)
  - 1986-1987, 24 folders (Box 3)
  - 1988
    - Minutes and Agendas (Box 4)
    - Chronological, 12 folders (Box 4)
  - 1989
    - Minutes and Agendas (Box 4)
    - Chronological, 9 folders (Box 4)
  - 1990
    - Minutes and Agendas (Box 4)
  - 1991
    - Minutes and Agendas (Box 4)
    - Chronological, 4 folders (Box 4)
  - 1992
    - Minutes and Agendas (Box 4)
    - Chronological, 4 folders (Box 4)
  - 1993
    - Chronological, 4 folders (Box 4)
  - 1994
    - Minutes and Agendas (Box 5)
    - Chronological, 4 folders (Box 5)
  - 1995
    - Chronological, 4 folders (Box 5)
  - 1996
    - Minutes and Agendas (Box 5)
    - Chronological, 4 folders (Box 5)
  - 1997
    - Minutes and Agendas (Box 5)
    - Chronological, 4 folders (Box 5)
    - Disarmament/Nuclear Freeze, 3 folders (Box 5)
  - 1998
    - Minutes and Agendas (Box 6)
    - Chronological, 4 folders (Box 6)
    - Disarmament/Nuclear Freeze, 2 folders (Box 6)
    - Guide to Farm Produce (Box 6)
  - 1999
    - Minutes and Agendas (Box 6)
    - Chronological (Box 6)
    - Disarmament/Nuclear Freeze (Box 6)
  - 2000
    - Chronological, 2 folders (Box 6)
    - Disarmament/Nuclear Freeze, 2 folders (Box 6)
  - 2001
    - Minutes and Agendas (Box 6)
    - Chronological, 4 folders (Box 6)
    - Disarmament/Nuclear Freeze, 2 folders (Box 23)
  - 2002
    - Minutes and Agendas (Box 23)
    - Chronological, 4 folders (Box 23)
    - Disarmament/Nuclear Freeze (Box 23)
  - 2003
    - Minutes and Agendas (Box 23)
    - Chronological, 4 folders (Box 23)
    - Disarmament/Nuclear Freeze (Box 23)
  - 2004
    - Minutes and Agendas (Box 23)
    - Chronological, 4 folders (Box 23)
  - 2005
    - Chronological (Box 23)
  - 2006
    - Chronological, 4 folders (Box 23)
  - 2007
    - Minutes and Agendas (Box 23)
    - Chronological, 4 folders (Box 23)
  - 2008
    - Minutes and Agendas (Box 23)
    - Chronological, 4 folders (Box 23)
  - 2009
    - Chronological (Box 23)
  - 2010
    - Chronological (Box 23)
- Topical Files
  The Topical Files series (8 linear feet) was originally created as a reference file for various anti-war activities and is arranged alphabetically by subject. Because many of the activities were sponsored by either CALC or ICPJ, this series contains much overlapping CALC and ICPJ material. Most of the material from the 1990s and 2000s relates to the ICPJ's Middle East Task Force and Hiroshima Day observances.
  - 1967-2005 1967-1976
    - Abortion 1974-1975 (Box 7)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition for a New Foreign Policy 1975-1976 (Box 7)
    - Air Force Recruiting Protests 1971-1973 (Box 7)
    - American Friends Service Committee 1967-1974 (Box 7)
    - American Report Mailing List (Box 7)
    - Amnesty 1972-1975
      - Canada 1973 (Box 7)
      - Ann Arbor News Advertisement 1972-1974 (Box 7)
      - Church Relations 1973 (Box 7)
      - Clergy and Laity Concerned 1973-1974 (Box 7)
      - General 1974 (Box 7)
      - Local 1970-1975, 2 folders (Box 7)
    - Ann Arbor 1972-1973 (Box 7)
    - Annual Meeting 1991-1999, 9 folders (Box 7)
    - Anti-ballistic Missile 1968-2000, 3 folders (Box 7)
    - Asian Scholars Petition 1973 (Box 7)
    - Bangladesh University Fiduciary 1996 (Box 7)
    - Bendix 1967, 1972-1973 (Box 7)
    - Bishops Call for Peace (United Methodist) 1974-1975 (Box 7)
    - Black Issues 1969-1970 (Box 7)
    - Brazil 1973 (Box 7)
    - Breaking Bread 1975 (Box 7)
    - Perry Bullard 1973-1974 (Box 7)
    - Center for Interchurch Cooperation 1974-1975 (Box 7)
    - Central Committee for Conscientious Objectors 1974-1975 (Box 7)
    - Central Intelligence Agency 1974-1975 (Box 7)
    - George Chauncey 1977-1978 (Box 7)
    - Chile (Box 7)
    - Church Statements on Vietnam 1972 (Box 7)
    - Church Women United 1974-1975 (Box 7)
    - Citizen's Delegation to Paris 1971 (Box 7)
    - Civil Liberties 1971, 1975-1976 (Box 7)
    - Committee of Concerned Asian Scholars 1975 (Box 7)
    - Congress 1973-1974 (Box 7)
    - Congress and War 1973 (Box 7)
    - Congregations
      - Bethlehem Church 1999-2000 (Box 7)
      - Beth Israel Congregation 1993-2004 (Box 7)
      - Brown Chapel (Box 7)
      - Campus Chapel 2003 (Box 7)
      - First Baptist Church 2000-2003 (Box 7)
      - First Congregational UCC 2003 (Box 7)
      - First Methodist Church 1995 (Box 7)
      - First Presbyterian Church 1992-2002 (Box 7)
      - First United Methodist Church 2000 (Box 7)
      - St. Andrews Episcopal Church 1997 (Box 7)
      - St. Francis of Assisi Catholic Church 1996-2003 (Box 7)
      - Temple Beth Emeth 2004 (Box 7)
      - Trinity Lutheran Church 1995-2000 (Box 7)
      - Zion Lutheran Church 1995-2003 (Box 7)
    - Congregational Giving 1992-2000 (Box 7)
    - Congregational Outreach 1987-2004 (Box 7)
    - Corporate Responsibility 1973-1975 (Box 7)
    - Creating a New Society 1970 (Box 7)
    - Dow Campaign 1968-1969, 2 folders (Box 7)
    - Draft 1967-1971
      - Ann Arbor Draft Counseling Center 1967-1969 (Box 8)
      - General 1967-1971, 5 folders (Box 8)
      - Michigan Draft Exchange 1969 (Box 8)
      - Petition to Free Two Draft Resisters from Prison 1974 (Box 8)
    - Environmental Research in Michigan 1971-1975 (classified research), 6 folders (Box 8)
      (includes tapes)
    - Esch, Marvin 1967-1975, 3 folders (Box 8)
    - Farm Workers Unionization 1976-1978 (Box 8)
    - Fellowship of Reconciliation
      - Undated (Box 8)
      - 1968-1976, 5 folders (Box 8)
    - Friendshipment 1975 (People-to-People Aid project) (Box 8)
    - Fuller, Barbara 1969-1980
      - General 1969-1980, 2 folders (Box 8)
      - Handwritten Notes 1972-1974, 2 folders (Box 8)
    - Fundraising 1984-2004
      - Ann Arbor Friends Grant 2000-2004 (Box 8)
      - Bethlehem United Church of Christ Grant 2003-2005 (Box 8)
      - Bookstore Benefit Days 1994-1999 (Box 8)
      - Charlie King Benefit Concerts 1995-2004, 4 folders (Box 8)
      - Fundraising Appeal 1991-2004, 2 folders (Box 8)
      - Fundraising History 1986-1996 (Box 8)
      - Grants 1984-2000, 3 folders (Box 8)
      - Jackson Social Welfare Grant 2000-2004 (Box 9)
      - Major Donors Committee 1987-1993, 2 folders (Box 9)
    - General Motors 1970, 2 folders (Box 9)
    - Global Living 1974 (Box 9)
    - Griffin, Robert, Senator 1973-1976 (Box 9)
    - Gumbleton, Thomas, Bishop 1973 (Box 9)
    - Hart, Philip, Senator 1973-1976 (Box 9)
    - Hatfield-McGovern Amendments (Box 9)
    - Help Unsell the War Campaign 1971-1976, 3 folders (Box 9)
    - Hoa Binh Committee 1969-1970 (Vietnamese Neutrals) (Box 9)
    - Honeywell Campaign
      - Undated (Box 9)
      - 1972, 3 folders (Box 9)
      - 1973, 5 folders (Box 9)
      - 1974-75 (Box 9)
      - 1976-77 (Box 9)
    - Hoosiers For Peace 1973-1974 (Box 9)
    - Human Rights 1976-1978 (Box 9)
    - Human Survival 1970 (Box 9)
    - Hunger 1974-1978, 2 folders (Box 9)
    - Impact: Legislative Information 1970-1973 (Box 9)
    - Impeach Nixon 1973 (Box 9)
    - Indochina Mobile Education Project 1974-1976 (Box 9)
    - Indochina Peace Campaign 1973-1975 (Box 9)
    - Inside Out (publication of Prisoners' Progress Association), 1975 (Box 9)
    - Institute For Non-Violence 1974 (Box 9)
    - Interfaith Council (Ann Arbor)
      - Undated (Box 9)
      - 1967-1971, 7 folders (Box 9)
      - 1972-1978, 5 folders (Box 10)
    - Job Descriptions/Personnel 1986-2002 (Box 10)
    - Kansas City Conference 1972 (Box 10)
    - Korea 1975-1976 (Box 10)
    - Landmines 1997 (Box 10)
    - Mrs. Le Thi Anh 1966 (Box 10)
    - Lists (Box 10)
    - Local Groups 1967-1970 (Ann Arbor) (Box 10)
    - Lotus, 1970-1971 (Box 10)
    - Luce, Don 1974 (Box 10)
    - May Day 1971 (Box 10)
    - Media 1973 (Box 10)
    - Medical Aid to Indochina 1972-1975, 2 folders (Box 10)
    - Michigan Council to Repeal the Draft 1968-1971, 3 folders (Box 10)
    - Milan Prison 1973 (Box 10)
    - Military Industrial Complex 1972-1974 (Box 10)
    - Military Personnel Against the War 1968-1969, 2 folders (Box 10)
    - Military Spending 1967-1971, 2 folders (Box 10)
    - Mobilization Committee 1969-1970 (Box 10)
    - Moratorium Committee 1969-1970 (Box 10)
    - Mother's Day Ad Campaign 1970-1971 (Box 10)
    - NARMIC 1970-1973, 3 folders (Box 10)
    - National Coalition Against War, Racism and Repression 1970-1971 (Box 10)
    - Native Americans 1972 (Ann Arbor) (Box 10)
    - Nestles 1975-1978 (Box 10)
    - Newspaper Ads 1966-1973 (Box 10)
    - Non-violence 1967-1973 (Michigan) (Box 10)
    - Office Notes 1974 (Ann Arbor) (Box 10)
    - Paris Trip 1971 (Box 10)
    - Peace Center 1970 (Ann Arbor), 2 folders (Box 10)
    - Peacemaker, 1970-1972 (Box 11)
    - Peace Groups 1970-1973 (Box 11)
    - Pentagon 1971 (Box 11)
    - Peoples Coalition For Peace and Justice 1971-1974 (Box 11)
    - Peoples Peace Treaty 1971 (Box 11)
    - Petition to End the War (Box 11)
    - Political Prisoners 1973-1974 (South Vietnam) (Box 11)
    - Poor People 1970-1972 (Box 11)
    - Politics (Presidential) 1968, 2 folders (Box 11)
    - Prisoners 1973-1976 (U.S.) (Box 11)
    - Promoting Enduring Peace 1967-1976, 2 folders (Box 11)
    - Ransoms 1973-1974 (Box 11)
    - Relief Agencies 1970-1974 (Box 11)
    - Rose Hochman Memorial 2002 (Box 11)
    - Speakers 1968-1974, 2 folders (Box 11)
    - Studying about Peace and War 1969-1971 (Box 11)
    - Tax Resistance 1969-1975 (Box 11)
    - Third World Reader Service 1973-1975 (Box 11)
    - Thirtieth Anniversary (Box 11)
    - Torture Undated (Box 11)
    - University of Michigan 1969-1976
      - General 1971-1974 (Box 11)
      - Office of Ethics and Religion 1974-1976 (Box 11)
      - Office of Student Services 1970 (Box 11)
      - ROTC 1969-1970 (Box 11)
    - University Values Seminar 1975 (Box 11)
    - U.S.-China People's Friendship Organization 1975-1976 (Box 11)
    - Vietnam War 1966-1976
      - Vietnam and America, Conference in Ann Arbor 1971 (Box 11)
      - Effect on U.S. Society undated, 1966-1976, 9 folders (Box 11)
      - Peace Efforts 1969 (Box 11)
      - Vietnam Vets Against the War 1971-1974 (Box 11)
    - Vigil of Accountability 1970, 2 folders (Box 12)
    - Volunteer Army 1972-1975 (Box 12)
    - War Crimes 1969-1972 (Box 12)
    - War Resisters League 1970-1974 (Box 12)
    - Week of Concern 1974 (Box 12)
    - Welfare 1971-1973 (Box 12)
    - Wolf, Eric-Vietnamese Series, WUOM 1967, audio-tapes (Box 12)
    - Women's Rights 1974-1976 (Box 12)
    - Worship Literature 1966-1978 (Box 12)
    - Workshop 1973 (Box 12)
    - World Peace Tax Fund 1974-1976 (Box 12)
    - Zionism 1975 (Box 12)
  - 1977-2008 1990-2008
    - Alternative Defense Workshop 1988 (Box 12)
    - Classified Research 1986 (Box 12)
    - Fair Trade 2005 (Box 12)
    - Globalization 1999-2007 (Box 12)
    - Hague Appeal for Peace 1998-2001, 4 folders (Box 12)
    - Healthcare Campaign 2008 (Box 12)
    - Hiroshima Day 1990-2001, 6 folders (Box 13)
    - Middle East Task Force 1997-2002, 13 folders (Box 13)
    - Michigan Peace and Justice Directory (of similar organizations) Undated (Box 13)
    - Miscellaneous 1977-2001 (Box 13)
- Hunger Task Force
  The Hunger Task Force series (6 linear feet) also overlaps with the Chronology of the ICPJ and is divided into two subseries, Chronological Files and CROP Walk Topical Files. The Chronological Files subseries documents the Hunger Task Force subcommittee of the ICPJ and the hunger-related issues addressed and events conducted by the organization from 1974-2008. The CROP Walk Topical Files, dating from the mid-1990s, document the planning and execution of the Washtenaw County CROP Walk.
  - Chronological Files
    - 1974
      - General (Box 14)
      - Walk (Box 14)
    - 1975
      - General (Box 14)
      - Walk (Box 14)
    - 1976
      - General (Box 14)
      - Walk (Box 14)
    - 1977
      - Conference April 22-23, 1977, 2 folders (Box 14)
      - CROP (Michigan) (Box 14)
      - Hunger Attitude Survey (Box 14)
      - Congregations
        - Beth Israel (Box 14)
        - Bethel AME (Box 14)
        - Calvary United Methodist (Box 14)
        - Christian Reformed (Box 14)
        - Church of the Good Shepherd (Box 14)
        - Fellowship of the Acts (Box 14)
        - First Baptist (Box 14)
        - First Congregational (Box 14)
        - First Presbyterian (Box 14)
        - First Unitarian (Box 14)
        - First United Methodist (Box 14)
        - Glacier Way Methodist (Box 14)
        - Lord of Light Lutheran. (Box 14)
        - Memorial Christian (Box 14)
        - Mennonite (Box 14)
        - Northside Presbyterian (Box 14)
        - Packard Road Baptist (Box 14)
        - St. Aidan's Episcopal (Box 14)
        - St. Andrew's Episcopal (Box 14)
        - St. Mary's Catholic Student Chapel (Box 14)
        - St. Patrick's Catholic (Box 14)
        - St. Thomas Catholic (Box 14)
        - Society of Friends (Box 14)
      - Contact People (Box 14)
      - Final Report (Box 14)
      - Final Report (draft) (Box 14)
      - General, 2 folders (Box 14)
      - Speakers (Box 14)
      - Walk, 2 folders (Box 14)
    - 1978
      - CROP (Box 14)
      - General (Box 14)
      - Hunger Event Telephone Feedback (Box 14)
      - Walk, 2 folders (Box 14)
    - 1979
      - Conference February 3, 1979 (Box 14)
      - General (Box 14)
      - Walk (Box 14)
    - 1980
      - General (Box 14)
    - 1981
      - General (Box 14)
      - Land, Food and Justice (Box 14)
    - 1982
      - General (Box 14)
      - Land, Food and Justice (Box 14)
    - 1983
      - General (Box 14)
      - Land, Food and Justice (Box 14)
    - 1984
      - General (Box 15)
      - Land, Food and Justice (Box 15)
    - 1985
      - General (Box 15)
      - Land, Food and Justice (Box 15)
    - 1992 (and earlier)
      - CROP Walk (Box 15)
    - 1993
      - CROP Walk (Box 15)
    - 1994
      - CROP Walk (Box 15)
    - 1995
      - CROP Walk (Box 15)
    - 1996
      - CROP Walk (Box 15)
    - 1997
      - CROP Walk (Box 15)
    - 1998
      - CROP Walk (Box 15)
    - 1999
      - CROP Walk (Box 15)
    - 2000
      - CROP Walk (Box 15)
    - 2001
      - CROP Walk (Box 15)
    - 2002
      - CROP Walk (Box 15)
    - 2003
      - CROP Walk (Box 15)
    - 2004
      - CROP Walk (Box 15)
    - 2005
      - CROP Walk (Box 15)
    - 2006
      - CROP Walk (Box 15)
    - 2007
      - CROP Walk (Box 15)
    - 2008
      - CROP Walk (Box 15)
  - CROP Walk Topical Files
    - Archives 1990-1997 (Box 15)
    - Arrangements Committee
      - 1978-1996 (Box 15)
      - 1998 (Box 15)
    - Awards 1998 (Box 15)
    - Bread For the World
      - 1995-1997, 3 folders (Box 15)
    - Brochures
      - 1994 (Box 16)
      - 1996 (Box 16)
      - 1998-2002, 5 folders (Box 16)
      - 2003-2008 (Box 16)
    - Bulletin inserts 1998-2002 (Box 16)
    - Bulletin, Walk Day 2000-2005 (Box 16)
    - Business (Box 16)
    - Committee Packs undated (Box 16)
    - Constituent Interpreter (Box 16)
    - Coordinating Committee
      - 1985-1993 (Box 16)
      - 1995-1997 (Box 16)
      - 1999-2002, 4 folders (Box 16)
    - Correspondence and Contacts (Box 16)
    - Correspondence and Copy File 1998 (Box 16)
    - Church World Service Board (Box 16)
    - Church World Service Grant Applications
      - 1985 (Box 16)